is going to be.
I am just going to say this is going to
come from Steve and Ramesh, right?
They are going to create this landing
page. Just to give you an idea, the user,
once they log into the links,
they would come into this launch.
It's going to be based on the ID,
those who are involved in planning.
Right, they would come to this page.
Okay,
but this is for which user have this view.
Jack.
That is what I'm saying,
those who are involved in planning.
So this is for admin user, right?
The super admin, right?
Not super user.
Say,
super user might go into user management.
Right, user management page.
Okay.
But which user usually use this this
screen?
That is what I'm saying, planning,
the people who are involved in planning
Planning.
activities, right? So go.
And this is for internal or external?
Inter, okay, intern, okay, yeah.
Internal, Odyssey internal.
Odyssey internal planning. Similarly,
this page, say,
right now I don't think we are exposing
this page to any external user, right?
It's all going to be internal user.
Got it. Okay.
Right? So when someone comes,
it's going to direct them.
So let's take the scenario where Odyssey
planners are going to come.
Once they come,
they will come into this launch page.
This is the first screen, right?
They can select.
Yeah,
so this is the requirement that Steve and
Okay.
Ramesh will provide you.
Okay, got it.
Brate?
Yeah,
because this is just before the order
page, right? So once they come in,
this is an idea, right?
It's not like something that's finalized.
This is the initial idea that what we
Yeah, okay.
came up with, right? Yeah. One,
they can search by customer, right?
You can see here,
they already have by default all
customers.
They have mixed customers by default and
they can select.
customers.
My customers is I would work only for
this particular customer.
I will only for work this for customer,
right? There could be like 5,
000 customers.
I may not be responsible for all these
customers, right?
So they can select those customers.
Once they select the customers,
Okay.
they can probably make it as a preference
and they can start it and they don't have
to look up every time.
So, whatever that, right?
How many customer the list could be
displayed?
I don't know,
those are all the requirements that will
come from them. I'm just saying,
I'm just giving you the idea, right?
Okay.
So this is not my page.
I'm just giving you the idea.
So I'm just giving you the user flow,
right? How it might be,
so that it's easy for you to grasp, right?
So once they come here,
Okay, got it.
they will be able to select.
So once they select the customer,
there will be...
different option screens, right?
Screens means these are all the launch.
Okay.
Say if I want to enter into orders,
I can select this, right?
It will have some metrics,
it will display the metrics.
So I'll select here.
Shipments have 3 monitoring areas.
Yeah.
One is a PGI,
probably you have already seen that
screen, right? PGI screen.
Okay, good.
All right, one second.
And which is a Jira story related to this
screen?
Which one? This one? That is,
that's why I'm saying they have to write
A.
it.
That's why I'm telling you it's not
related to me.
Ah, they they have to write. Is this not?
There are not any.
Any Jira story so far?
Yeah, right now, right now,
I don't think there is any Jira story for
them.
They have written anything related to
this one.
I'm just giving you an idea so that I can,
when I tell you that these are related to
some related questions,
Okay.
so that's why I'm telling you the
background so that you are aware of the
background, how it works, right?
OK, Desk.
Yeah,
is this only a draught to talk with the
business, right?
Yeah,
just I need a wireframe to talk to the
business. I don't need a VD.
That's what I'm telling you, right? See,
this is how they are coming in. Right now,
you see a dashboard, nothing is there,
Yeah, yeah.
right?
So they should come here and something
should be like this, right?
They should be able to select.
Once they select these options, right,
you see here order management,
All right.
it will take them to order.
If they click within shipments,
there are different areas,
say shipment planning,
shipment monitoring, and then PGIPGR.
Yeah.
We already have PGIPGR. I'll go to errors,
right? This is PGIPGR.
You see here all these grids.
So it means that when they launch these,
Yeah.
right,
so they will get all these grids in the
path.
top and they can click on these grids and
the bottom table refreshes. You see that?
Yeah.
Right? That's how it is working, right?
And then I can collapse all this and just
work on the ones that I wanted to work,
right? So this is how it is going to be.
So this is PGI. When I launch PGI,
three of these PGI metrics will be
available to the user, right?
Once I click,
all these three will be available.
So it will be the error related,
it will be...
PGI manual error and then this is related
to rating error.
All these will be available to the users
during this PGI, right?
Iris.
So now we are going to only talk about
this screen, right? The planning.
Yeah,
but but when you when you go to PGI and
it show and it show you this metric is
because they selected the metrics at the
Mhm.
first time, right?
This is a metric that they selected.
Yeah, the PGI here, you see here,
missed pickup, delayed. Yeah,
Yeah, yeah.
it's all here, right?
So these metrics are here.
Yeah, they selected.
So they selected here and then say launch,
right? Once they launch,
all these will be available to the user
on the top section, right?
And probably it'll go and sit on the
order management by default.
Yeah.
I'm just saying by default it might sit
on the order management, right?
And then if they wanted to go to a
different one,
they can click on this and this one will
get loaded, right?
So if they wanted to go to shipments,
they will click on the shipment and then
the shipment will get loaded.
Makes sense? The flow?
So they will come here, select the user.
So now there is a user combination and
the screen combination established here.
Once they click that,
then it will go by default,
sit on order management, load it.
But if I wanted to start...
Only for that customer.
Ah, only for that customer,
selected customer, right?
All right, okay.
Right? So now for that customer,
if I want to go into shipment exceptions,
I can click here and then this table grid
will be loaded, right?
So what we are going to see right now is
only this, right?
Yeah.
I'm not going to talk about orders.
I'm going to just go on to talk about
shipment exceptions.
We'll come to monitoring.
This solution is not.
over yet.
So we will come to exceptions only under
exceptions.
We are going to see how and what will
happen. Okay, clear?
Yeah, clear.
Okay, so next going to the screen.
This is how we wanted the design,
but I'll let you have the design, right?
Come up with the design, right?
Yeah.
How we wanted it.
So when we come to shipment exceptions,
these are the categories under which the
shipment exceptions will be, right?
So there are date issues,
there are routing review issues.
then tender issues, tender review,
bid review, right?
Okay.
These are all the issues that will be
under exceptions.
The user will have to work through each
of these exceptions,
resolve the shipment so that they can
find a carrier.
The main objective here is that they need
to find a carrier for a shipment.
That's all, right?
So if they only resolve these issues,
Yeah.
they will be able to find a carrier,
right?
It might have come from because of
different reasons. The date issues,
when it was trying to go and tender,
it said, it made some cheque saying that,
okay,
I'm not able to tender because the date
is not.
Perfect.
I won't be able to find a carrier for
this date.
And so it comes and sits in this
exception and the user needs to either
fix the date or find a better carrier.
Got it, yeah.
Right? So similarly, routing review,
say for example,
one case where routing is not at all
available, right? I cannot tender at all,
right?
So that needs a user review so that those
kind of shipments will sit under this
category.
Okay.
Right? Just like here,
how they are able to load a specific set
of error, by clicking on that,
they should be able to philtre down to
that shipment.
Okay, yeah.
Like, yeah, you see four,
then only four of the shipments will get
loaded here, right? You see that?
Yeah, how can I?
Yeah, so maybe this is showing three,
but let me change it to...
I don't know why it is showing only three
when it said four,
but idea is you got the idea, right?
It should show only four shipments here,
right? So it should be clickable.
Once they click,
the table should be able to.
If they click outside,
the entire shipment should be displayed.
The first one,
they won't have the bottom screen.
Right,
so it'll be coming out like the entire
grid if I click on this.
If I click on this one,
if I click on this, it has 91, right?
So it would display, it is 91 errors,
it is not like 91 shipments,
Yeah.
it is 91 errors.
So it will list all of this,
so it is having 60,
so all of this is getting displayed here.
Okay.
Right, so it should display, but if,
as I click on each of those,
only those needs to be filtered.
Yeah, but for, yeah, but for treatment,
it's a section and for the...
Understood?
For the white frame, how many section,
how many screens for this screen you need
to display that? I mean,
you need that I display.
Data issues, um, routing review.
Okay, got it.
you,
you just need to create a screen for me
like this,
but there are other screens which you
would need to create for each of these
tabs, right? I'll come back,
Okay.
I'll come to that.
You don't have to create,
like if I click on routing view,
you display only 7.
Okay.
I don't need all those things, right?
You just create a single like this, right?
You just show.
these and show that there are a couple of
shipments here.
I will voice over or when I talk to
business or we talk to business, right?
Yeah.
I when I can voice over on that,
I can show them these.
Those are waste of time to do that, right?
We don't need that. Okay. So wireframe,
Gar.
we don't need all those.
It's just to get that. Okay. So.
If you see here, these are quick filters.
User can click on each of these or they
can click on each of these quick filters,
right? You see here?
All right.
So it will do the same thing, nothing,
no other difference, right? And...
Yep.
But this is tops of feathers.
Help.
Uh, I live section, data issue, routing,
review - is this?
Tabs, right? So, if I got...
Yeah, tabs, tabs like here, like this.
Okay.
Yeah, they work like a filter,
but they they are a tabs.
Yeah, they work as a, yeah,
this is a query. It runs a query behind.
Yeah, yeah, it is a filter,
but I need to display them like a tabs,
Yeah.
right?
Yeah, tabs, yeah, like what you see here,
right? Okay, so these same things,
Yeah, got it.
we have it here for the user to click.
Then I'll come to the grid,
Okay.
then we will come to the top section.
So this is a by shipment, right?
There is no sell shipment here.
This is a by shipment, correct?
I had an initially,
I had a cell shipment here.
Maybe I'll just introduce that column.
If you see here,
all the column lists are here.
You see here?
Yeah.
by shipment, sell shipment.
I just kept important ones here to show,
right? If you can refer to the next one,
just include the sell shipment alone in
the next column next to the buy shipment,
right?
Because we just got it today only I got a
requirement saying that by sell shipment
will be created immediately a buy
shipment is created, right?
Before currently the implementation is
sell shipment will be created.
after a carrier has been selected,
but that's not the case right now.
They would want to create the sell
shipment immediately by shipment.
So it is better to have a view of the
sell shipment. Okay,
so just introduce this column or I will
add,
put a note saying include sell shipment
here, but you can fix to this table,
right? You don't have to change anything.
Use the same header.
You can use same set of information,
just need a mock, right?
Okay.
right? And the table will look like this.
It won't show initially as a split screen,
right?
You see here how it is showing as a table.
Got it.
So the same way it needs to,
it should not show the split screen here.
Only when the user clicks on that
checkbox, right?
It should show up as split screen.
Like this in the bottom.
At the bottom, OK.
Right?
Like how it splits up on the screen.
Maybe I can show you.
Have you seen the ODM screen?
Yeah, it's just like an audience scream.
Yeah, it's, yeah,
they wanted the ODM screen, right?
So that's why I'm just taking that one so
that you can have a reference.
There is that ODM screen.
Yeah, right.
Just give me a second, let me log in.
How can I have access to ODM screen? ODM?
How can I have access to ODM platform?
Help.
ODM screen? Yeah, ODM screen.
I don't know. I got it from someone.
Yeah.
Someone applied it for me.
Okay, but it says it, I can,
can I write to IT?
Yeah, you can.
You can request with the...
The IT, yeah.
If you put a request with IT,
you should be able to get it, right?
Okay.
Right, yeah,
this is how the screen will be.
Yeah.
Right? You see the screen?
This is how you get loaded, right?
Okay, yeah.
But you don't have the top section.
We want the top section like this.
Okay.
right, the top section to be like this.
Once we launch,
we want it to come up here and then show
here and then have the entire table like
here displayed, right?
Like all the and display.
Yeah, and then once they click on this,
show details, right?
The bottom screen displays.
You see different tabs.
Yeah.
Right, yeah,
that is what we are going to go with,
right? So, similarly,
you have you will have different tabs at
the bottom, right?
Each tab is going to show some
representation, correct? So,
so that for this for this particular
But, but...
shipment, what is its order information?
But which information I need to display
in the bottom? I mean...
For the selected one,
you will be able to select only one at a
time.
Yeah, yeah, only one at a time for a, for,
for, for wide frame, but only one tap,
right?
Only the information for only one tap,
right? Like...
So whatever line has been selected, right?
In this case,
I selected for this by shipment, right?
This by shipment can be coming from an
Yeah.
order, right?
Shipment doesn't automatically originate.
It comes from an order.
Okay.
Correct? Always it starts with an order,
right?
If the user would want to know what are
all its order information,
say a shipment can have multiple loads in
it. I don't know whether you under,
you know all those concepts.
Do you know those concepts?
No.
Okay, I don't know,
there's a lot of things I need might have
Yeah.
to explain. Okay, okay, let me,
I'll put it very simple, right?
Yeah.
So this is,
this is how an order gets created, right?
Order.
Okay, this is easier to explain for me.
Let me go here.
Okay.
Okay, so an order is created. Forget,
there is no order here.
Yeah.
Whenever an order is created,
a load is created, right?
Okay.
A load comes in the new.
Then when the load goes,
Yeah.
always has a shipment, right?
A shipment is created for a load.
Okay.
Imagine like this, right?
OK, let me put it.
An order is here.
Then you have a load.
Every order will have its have a load,
right?
Yeah.
And then this as a shipment.
Right.
Geta.
Right, load sits inside a shipment, right?
This is a shipment.
N.
load sits inside a shipment. Got it?
So for every order,
OK, yeah, got it.
there is a load created.
Then once a load is created,
a shipment is created,
the shipment is mapped to this one.
So the shipment holds the load. OK?
Okay.
Understood?
Yeah, understood.
Okay, this is on the buy side.
Okay.
Right? On the cell side,
it happens the same way, right?
Instead of load,
it will have a reference to the order.
Right,
this order map is get mapped to the sell
side, right?
Because sell is for the customer,
buy is for the carrier, right?
So for the sell shipment,
Okay.
it gets mapped to the order, right?
So it has an order,
because you're talking to the customer,
they need order reference.
So that is why order is getting mapped.
on the sell side. So it has a shipment,
it has an order. So it has a shipment,
it is an order.
This is a different number,
this is a different number,
and order is order reference number.
Make sense so far?
Yeah, but,
but it's the same or it's the same order
number, but it's different shipment name.
Yeah, correct. Instead of putting a load,
we are mapping the same order because
Chidman number.
customer sent the order, right?
As I told you, sell is for customer.
Yeah.
Right, and by is for carrier.
Okay.
Right?
So what we are talking right now is only
by side, right? Only for carrier.
Because once an order is created,
Only that this side.
we create a load and then have a shipment.
For this, I need to find a carrier, right?
I need to fix a carrier for this load.
Someone needs to come and pick it up.
Yeah.
Right,
that is why the customer had given the
Yeah.
shipment order food to us, right?
You find a carrier for this and you make
Yeah.
an arrangement.
That is why they have given this.
So, in order to make find a carrier,
we are trying to do certain steps.
Sure.
Okay.
Right?
That is what I'm trying to explain to you,
what those steps are.
Brate.
Well, yeah.
One other thing is, right,
and Odyssey can do like this as well,
right? Always it starts like this.
Let's say, forget about cell, right?
I'll remove the cell.
Right? Imagine there is another order.
Okay.
Right, or two?
Order 2, okay.
Order 2. It is for the same customer.
Let's take the scenario that this is for
the same customer.
The same customer.
Yeah, ABC.
He created two orders.
Yeah, he created two orders, right? ABC,
ABC gave two orders, right?
Okay.
We also do the same thing, right?
We create a shipment for it and a load.
I'll say load one.
I love to.
Load 2, right?
That.
Sorry, load one, load two.
Sorry, look two, right?
But what we can do is, as planning,
Don't worry.
we can put it in one shipment.
Okay.
Right,
and find one carrier instead of finding 2
carriers.
Ohh.
Are you getting the point?
Smart, yeah, very smart.
It is saving for the customer, right? Say,
imagine it is getting picked up on the
Yeah.
same day,
needs to be delivered to the same address,
right?
Yeah.
Why would you need two different carriers?
One carrier can do it, right?
Yeah, it saves time and money.
So we can do that.
Saving time and money.
So that is what the planning activity is.
That is what we are doing in this
planning thing.
Good.
Right?
So we are trying to put these together,
together into a shipment and say that,
okay,
I am now planning these two together.
Similarly, it can be more as well, right?
It can be 3 loads, it can be 4 loads,
whatever it is, right? Say imagine,
imagine this one and two, right?
This is in one address and this is in a
different address,
but they are like 5 kilometres or five
miles apart.
Right?
Imagine that the address is only 5 miles
Okay.
apart.
It is getting picked up at the same
location,
but delivered into a two different
location. It is picking at that A, right?
And then going to B&C.
Right? You now get the point?
So load one and two is getting picked up
Yeah.
at A,
but it is load one is getting delivered
at B.
Okay.
And load 2 is getting delivered at sea.
Okay.
But same carrier,
the same carrier does that, right?
Say carrier is ODFL, right?
This carrier goes here to A,
Yeah.
picks up these, goes to B,
delivers it first,
and this is only 5 miles apart,
he goes to C and delivers it, right?
Yeah.
You get the point, correct?
So it can also happen. So instead of,
Sure.
Yeah, yeah.
sometimes it could be load one and two
should be delivered at B. I'm just saying,
it can happen that way,
or it needs to be delivered to a
different location.
This can happen like this as well, right?
Yeah.
Or it can also happen A1. I'll put it A1.
A one is 2 different pickup address.
This is pickup.
Yeah.
And this is drop.
Right? So it has two different, say,
doc one, doc two, right?
Okay.
So it gets picked up in these two address,
then first gets delivered.
Load one is getting picked up here, right?
Load one,
load two is getting picked up here.
Right?
And then load one is getting dropped at 2,
and load 2 is getting dropped at C, right?
All this can be planned here in the
shipment.
Hmm, and shipment planning.
Yeah, shipment planning. All this can be.
It started with two separate shipments.
Now it made into one shipment and there
are two loads in it.
Sure,
and how do you combine the low and seen
in one single shipment into the
application?
Yeah, we do that.
We already have implemented that.
So it'll say the system will take care of
that.
Yeah,
but how it's happened in the application?
Could you show me?
We can't show it is all back-end,
back-end activity right now.
Amends.
We don't have a front-end for it.
Okay.
Okay, it message comes from TMS.
Once a message comes from TMS,
it will delete the shipment,
move the load one to load two or load 2
to load one.
Yeah.
It will delete the shipment,
move this to load to. That's how it does.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah.
Understood, so far done.
Yeah, under some, yeah, so far, good.
Okay, okay, so far, let's go back here,
right? So in this circumstance,
what happens is...
There will be two orders, correct?
For this shipment,
Yeah.
there will be order one reference.
Order 1 reference and order 2 reference.
Make sense?
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah,
but this is the same the same order with
two reference, right?
No,
no shipment with shipment with order
to number reference.
reference, right? Say,
now the shipment has combined load one
and load two,
so it is order one and order two
reference for it, correct?
Yeah, in one single shipment. Okay,
got it.
Correct. It has a load. I told you,
if you remember,
Yeah.
on the cell side we are referencing,
where did we go there?
Yeah.
I showed you somewhere else, right?
The cell side we are referencing.
Where did we talk about that one?
I forgot, right?
Yeah, you, you, you, you believe it,
don't worry.
Yeah,
on the sell side we are mapping the order,
right?
On the buy side we are mapping the load.
Yeah.
Yeah, got it.
So on the buy side,
we are talking only buy side. So buy,
even though it order one and order two,
see load is mapped to an order, right?
Because I told you,
the load is created from an order, right?
It already has a relationship.
And the shipment and load has a
Yeah.
relationship because shipment is created
for a load.
Correct,
so it knows all that relationship.
Yeah, yeah.
Right?
So when you move a load one and load 2 to
a shipment,
so this shipment has a relationship
automatically to order one and order two
because order load one is related to
order one and load 2 is related to order
two and shipment is related to load one
and load two and so shipment knows order
one and order two. Make sense?
Makes sense.
Right? Okay, now let's go back.
I told you all the basics right now. Okay,
Yeah.
so...
So in the buy shipment, right,
the user would want to see how many
orders are mapped, right?
If they click on here and click on the
Yeah.
order tab,
they will be able to see two orders.
You see here?
Yeah.
Right? So if I go to OTM,
it is a similar behavior. I don't know.
Here it doesn't have like that, right?
Okay, it's not showing up here.
It's just showing one order.
Maybe this has only one order, right?
But you got the point, right?
So if I have this particular buy shipment
has two or more orders,
I would like to see the order number.
And if I click on S2,
it should display only the S2 information,
right? That's why you see a V mark,
a small V I have added here.
Yeah.
that V represents that if I click on that,
it will drop down two of the order number
and the user will be able to click on S2
or they will be able to click on A and 7.
Make sense?
Alright, yeah, this is a drop-down,
and you can select different number.
Correct, correct. So, ah, correct.
You got my point, right? So then,
Of the orders.
because it is hard to show,
otherwise I need to create another tab
Yeah, yeah.
for another order, right?
It will be difficult.
So what I did was I put a dropdown so
that it will tell you in the dropdown how
Yeah.
many orders are mapped.
to the shipment.
Yeah.
Is this for orders you can have?
Just like what we talked about.
Right, right here we have two.
Three, 3 number, 4 number in the menu.
Correct. Exactly. You got it. Right?
So if I click on S2600,
Yeah.
it should show the display of all the
information related to the order. Right?
Okay.
Okay. So I need,
say what I want from the order is I need
the general section, you know, order.
Let me go here.
Right,
it already has some information up in
this.
If you see this order section,
it has some general information, right?
Yeah.
So long. I need general information,
reference, pickup, delivery,
all this to be displayed here.
In this section, right?
The right makes sense.
All right, okay. Yeah, the same section,
yeah, yeah,
the same section of the final version of
folder.
Ah, you are there, Efrain, you got it,
right? So if I click on this,
Yeah.
it should show these sections underneath
that, right? Not the product information.
I got the product information separately,
right?
Only the general section until this point.
This is product info, right?
I don't need the product info.
I need until this.
Yeah.
Okay.
Right,
so the general reference pickup consignee,
right? For example, consigner, consignee,
and the planning,
Yeah.
all this should be displayed here.
Got it, yeah.
Right, so that I can have,
because I have a separate tab for product.
You see here a separate tab for product.
Okay.
Yeah, you have separate tab for Pro,
and you can see everything in in the in
this tab.
Right, right, right side.
So if I click on AN,
it will bring the order information from
there.
Yeah.
Okay, so far clear. So right now, yeah,
so this is 1 tab.
Sure, so far clear.
I'll just explain each tab what is the
requirement so that you will be clear
about it, right? Okay,
so once we come up here, these are all,
I'll just explain the information here.
So we talked about by shipment.
By shipment, sorry.
Yeah.
Customer information would be out here.
Got it, yeah,
because this is for only for that.
Right?
Correct, exactly right.
Or I can also do combination of customer.
I can select these two customers,
but you are very,
it's very straightforward.
Like an order will be from one customer.
It cannot be combination of customers,
right? Only A shipment can be combination.
Say if a shipment is there, I might have.
You right now assume that,
assume that I can I cannot cross
Only one cost.
consolidate right?
A different customer's order cannot be
put with another customer's order,
so it'll be either the shipment is also
will be for one customer only. Got it?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, so order number,
if there are three or more orders,
that order number should be displayed
here.
Okay.
Right, so here we have two orders,
so that's why I've given here 2 orders.
Yeah.
Right,
and order count how many orders it is
saying, right?
Maybe it is better to do this, OK?
Yes, so one single.
This is just a mark. Yeah,
this is one single order, right?
So pickup date.
It will have a pickup date coming from
the order, right?
It will tell what is the pickup date.
It will tell you what is the delivery
date, from which location,
we talked about it, right?
From which location it needs to be picked
up from, right? Pickup. Say if you have...
Two pickup,
you'll just go tell the what is the first
pickup, right? This is the first pickup,
right? This is the second pickup.
Yeah.
We'll come to that one next, right?
So it'll just add, tell what is the,
this pickup will be the first pickup.
Where is that?
A pickup,
pickup date and time will be the first
Yeah, but...
pickup date and time.
Yeah, but in this case,
if we will have two pickup day,
Pareek.
No, no, no,
we'll have only the first pickup. Always,
we will have two.
we'll show only the first pickup.
Okay.
And what happened with the second pickup?
This is not if played?
No, not here, not in the grid.
If you put too many information,
Okay.
it will be confusing, right?
So that is why we are not putting in all
Yeah.
that information.
I'll show you where we will show it,
right?
If you see a stops and appointments.
Yeah.
Yeah, inside that,
I will show all the detail.
So pick up one, pick up two, delivery.
So all these, it is getting,
so in this case, right,
it has two pickups,
pick up one and pick up two,
but delivering at point B, right?
Help.
Imagine that scenario, right?
It will show up like this.
Okay.
Yeah.
Pick up one, pick up two, delivery,
and what order number it is getting
Okay.
picked up,
from where it is getting picked up, zip,
country, right? State, zip, and country.
It is going to give that right example.
I've given you example here, right?
And the date where and when it is going
to get picked up, appointment time, date.
volume, package quantity,
and pickup number, if any information.
So this we want to give it to the user as
pickup number one, pickup #2,
Yeah.
and delivery #3, right?
This is one form of it.
Okay.
It could also be displayed as two pickups,
right? Here we have two pickups.
We show as pickups and delivery in the
next column instead of like continuous
thing, right?
Pickup will be in one sequence and
delivery will be in sequence. See,
it is just an alternate format I added
Okay.
here.
Yeah.
Understood? So on top of that,
it will tell you what is the total miles
Yeah, I understand.
it is going to cover,
what is the gross weight of the shipment,
volume of the shipment, then acceptance,
accepted carrier,
which carrier has accepted this, right?
The seed equipment, utilization,
all this information it is going to give.
Right in this top section, right?
Where is it stops in appointments?
Okay.
Right? The stops and appointments,
that is why I added a separate tab here
Yeah.
and say stopper stops and appointments.
It is going to give all this appointment
is here, right? Appointment is here.
This is the first pickup.
What order is getting picked up here,
right?
From which location it is getting picked
up. The information is here.
date it is going to pick up.
Right,
and if it is an if it is already planned,
Aha.
like appointment and all those things are
given,
so it is it will give you this
information as well.
Date available if planning this RSD,
right? What is that?
RSD is requested delivery date, right?
Based on.
requested delivery date or requested
pickup date, right? So based on that,
Okay.
you just use this format,
but I'm just giving you the idea, right?
Yeah.
Okay, so now we covered the pickup date.
So that is why I'm saying we are not
going to give all of the pickup date
because that is going to be available.
Say here we have two pickup dates,
but we don't have to give both the pickup
dates, right? We just give one,
the first pickup date, say August 20th.
That is what will be available here.
Okay, sure.
Right?
The delivery date will be the last
delivery. This delivery date.
If there are two deliveries,
we will take the last one.
Just how the pickup,
we took the first one for the delivery,
we will take the last one. Right?
Yeah.
In this case, there's only one delivery.
The delivery is August 22nd.
So if you look here,
it should say August 22nd.
Right, OK. Origin,
origin is again the first pickup origin,
Yeah.
right?
What is the pickup we talked here about?
Where is that? States, zip, and country,
Sure.
right?
Yeah, I have a question. Why,
if this is the right, I mean,
For pickup.
the right word is pick up,
why in order we can talk about consignor
and consignor and consigning?
Yeah, we can do that. Say,
this is pickup date, right?
In.
We can, we can call,
we can call the pickup on delivery, right?
This is pickup and delivery, correct?
I mean...
Yeah, but this is related to, I mean,
could you go back to the order order view?
order view. I don't have order view. Oh,
here.
Yeah, that.
No, uh...
Here?
This, yeah, this one, this one. I mean,
if, if this,
if this section is where is that the
title is pick up on delivery,
why we use the word consigner and
consigning?
Consigner is shipper,
shipper and consignee is who is receiving
If...
it, right?
Yeah, but yeah,
but we can call them like pickup and
deliveries is more directly, right?
Yeah, we can, yeah,
you need to talk to Steve.
Yeah, it's just more direct click.
I understand that this is a synonyms,
Correct, correct.
but we can call them like that.
Correct, correct. Yeah, what is it? See,
exactly why I'm telling you all this
because you can make the design
consistent, right?
You can point me saying that, okay,
they're using this terminology,
Yeah.
they're using this one,
or something is different in this area,
you want to take a look at it.
Something you can tell me.
No, it's just, it is the best for me,
it's the best,
the best explanation that I have so far
of everything related to order treatments
and carriers. This is really good.
Thank you for that. Yeah.
OK, no problem. You'll come. Yeah, OK.
My job is to explain to you so that you
can do a good job about designing, right?
Yeah, yeah, that's the idea, yeah.
Otherwise,
if I give you half-baked information,
how will you design?
Yeah.
Right, makes sense.
That's why I do a design so that I
Yeah, it makes sense.
understand clearly what it needs to be.
Yeah, yeah, you are right.
Yeah, right? Okay,
so this will be a pickup address,
so pickup date, delivery date.
Then it will be an origin.
Okay.
Origin is this particular pickup date
origin, right? Which state, city,
and zip code it is going to come from.
If you see here, this is the city,
Mm.
Yeah.
this is the state, this is the country.
And this one is the zip code, right?
So that is the zip code. Yeah, finally,
Yeah, Saikat.
as we talked about here, for the delivery,
what is the city, state, country,
and zip code?
Okay.
Right? Okay.
Gross weight is nothing but if you take
this, if you put these two loads together,
this load might weigh 1000 pounds.
This load may weigh 1000 pounds.
Together they weigh 2000 pounds, correct?
Okay.
Right,
the shipment will have that information.
Load will not tell you.
Load will tell you only its own weight.
This load will tell you its own weight,
but only the shipment can tell you what
is its total weight, correct?
Yeah, the total way, yeah.
Yeah, the total weight is here.
Gross weight will tell you 6000 pounds
for this by shipment.
Yeah.
Okay, then it has a mode.
What type of mode it is, right?
If it is a truckload or an LTL, right?
That is what its mode is. So in this case,
the mode is going to be truckload.
Right? Equipment.
Equipment is how it is going to be moved.
OHara.
Is it going to be moved by a dry van?
Is it going to be a refrigerated
truckload?
Or is it going to be a heated truckload?
How it is going to be moved, right?
So this gives you that description,
equipment.
Yeah.
Right,
SCAC is who is the carrier who is doing
it. We talked about here, right,
and stops.
Yeah.
Where is that SCAG? Somewhere we saw that.
Yeah.
What is my rate for this shipment?
Because this is an by shipment,
this is an AP cost, right?
What is the cost for the shipment?
So that will be there. And I have,
if you see here, I have change view,
right?
A click here so that I will be able to
manage my column.
All these are going to be my column.
right?
I don't want so much of to be displayed.
I want only minimal to be this,
but if the user would want to change the
table,
they should be able to add any of these
items using the change view. You see here?
And the change view example I've added
Yeah, yeah, I got it.
here.
You see here how I want that, but you can,
if what is available,
what has been selected,
you can move between left and right.
Yeah.
Got it.
Right?
So this change view is to control the
grid here, right?
And the download is download everything
Sure.
that is visible, right?
You can restrict it to say like 5000
records max.
Okay.
Whatever is visible only you can download.
Not all the fields, right?
Not all the fields.
Say if I selected only 10 fields,
No, Okay.
10 fields only we will be able to
download it.
Got it.
Okay, okay. Next for these, okay,
I'll come to here. What is OpenSearch,
right? See,
there is a certain things that I will be
able to search, but if I go here,
I can customise my search.
Say for example, here, right?
I've already customised my search,
correct? These are kind of filters.
Yeah.
But within tender issues, say for example,
I wanted to create a search only for
tender review.
Okay.
All right? Or if I wanted to search,
because if you see here,
there are different statuses for a
shipment. Shipment can be in hold,
shipment can be in optimization pool,
shipment can be in review,
shipment can be approved, right?
It is spot bid, bid review.
It can go in different statuses.
This is a state transition diagram.
right, for a shipment, right?
But you see here, you don't see that here.
Okay.
But if the user would want to see,
say for example, I'm a user, right?
If I want to see what are all the
shipments in my optimization pool,
I should be able to customise my own
query.
It is nothing but customising my query
here, right?
So I should be able to open search and
then save my search. Open searches,
I am customising my query,
and if I like my query,
I should be able to save it.
Okay.
Make sense?
Yeah, Maxim, but the...
I've given you an example here,
how you will be able to do it, right?
Jha.
See here.
Right, so you haven't.
This is an example of the of the search.
Search, correct. Say, save searches.
You can create save searches like this.
Say, or I can put an order number, right?
I can say for this particular order
number, I already I can run open date,
right? Open date, this date to this date,
search and apply, right? And then pick.
Okay.
Whatever it is being picked,
I can save it as one query for open date
query.
Okay, sure.
Right, right.
So those things can, once I add it,
I should be able to add my, sorry,
I should be able to add it under my saved
search here. And I clicked on save search,
it should display all that saved search
right here. You see here,
if I click on save search,
it will display all my saved search.
Yeah.
I can click on it and move.
and display it, right?
Then the grid will get loaded accordingly.
Okay.
Make sense?
Yeah, makes sense.
Okay,
so now we have covered the top section,
right? We covered this,
we covered all of this section,
and we covered this table as well, right?
So this information is nothing but the
Yeah.
table, the grid information,
all those data related to that shipment
will be available, right, to the user.
Okay.
So that is what I have added here, right?
I've added even explanation,
Okay.
whatever those explanations are, right?
Okay, we talked about the, okay,
Yeah.
all these ones, right?
We will go one by one.
We covered stops and appointments, right?
We did see if a shipment has multiple
pickups, it will show.
pick up, pick up, pick up one,
pick up two,
but if it has multiple deliveries,
it will show delivery one, delivery two,
Yeah.
right? That is what we saw here, right?
Pick up, stop one is pick up,
Yeah.
stop two is pick up,
stop three is delivery.
It stops here because there is only two
pickups and one delivery.
Suppose if it has another delivery.
Say for example,
whatever is picking up in second is going
to get delivered to a different address.
It will be stopped for delivery, right?
It will automatically do it.
But for the wireframe,
Yeah.
you can use the same example, right?
Okay.
So we covered stops, orders. Product,
whatever you have in orders, right?
This section, order section.
I would want the same mock to be used for
order for now, right? Say for example,
if you add a product, right,
then you have all these.
If you edit,
I don't know why you're not able to edit.
You should be able to edit this.
Bye.
Thanks.
Allah.
I think.
And link it. OK, if I edit it,
you see here.
Yeah.
You have all these general and product
information, correct?
I can also have Asmat.
So all this information should be
available here in the product section.
Right? I have given you examples as well.
In the product section, okay.
OK, that is a product, right?
What can be in the product, right?
So I want it to be in the grid view like
this, right?
And I've also given you the attributes,
right? Say for example,
Okay.
we talked about order here, right?
One order, 2 orders are here, right?
If I click similarly,
the product should also have like this,
right? When I click on product,
what my expectation, but you can design.
If this is the order number,
order has multiple lines, right?
It is possible, right?
Order can have two lines,
it can have one line,
it can have three lines,
whatever number of lines.
It has to have the order number.
Then what are all its line items
underneath it?
Then put that information together.
Similarly, if I click on plus,
it will expand.
So that is why I've given you this mock.
Make sense?
Okay, makes sense.
Yeah,
say product info to be organised as shown.
Each plus is representation of a line
number, order line, right?
So if I click on this plus,
the first one will be the first line,
but the user knows that seeing the plus,
there is more than one line, right?
If there is more,
if it is not more than one line,
the plus should not be there.
It should display only.
the order number and that line
information.
Yeah, sure. Maxim.
Makes sense?
And whatever I marked in green are the
ones that needs to be displayed in the
grid, right? Rest of the ones,
you can have it as customization, right?
Just like how we had here, the wheel,
you can put a wheel here and say that I
will be,
I will show you here so it's easy for you
to understand.
Where did it go?
Yeah, right. If I come to product,
you see here as a table,
this is how I want it, right?
But I want it with a plus. You see here,
Yeah.
there's A plus I added.
Where did it go? Product, product, ah,
plus. If it has multiple lines,
it needs to show there is,
here it is only one line, right?
Imagine it has second line,
there will be a plus,
and it will show only one line,
but the user clicks on plus,
it will drop down and show the second
line. Make sense?
Yeah, but the second line is 4.
Second line, same order.
You see here order number 11111111, right?
It has this one order. See,
we talked here, right?
Yeah.
We'll go back to this.
I think you are lost a little bit, right?
We talked about order,
we talked about load,
Yeah.
we talked about shipment, right? In order,
Yeah.
can have one line or multiple lines,
right?
Yeah.
You understand about line, right?
Line is like this.
Each product is one line.
Right, if I add another product,
it will be another line, right?
Hmmm.
If I add another one,
it will be another line,
But...
so each one will have its own.
But...
But why, why do you call them like a line?
This is not a line, right?
Mm.
Within the order, I'm saying,
what are all I'm shipping?
Okay.
Say, imagine you are going to a shop,
right? Say,
imagine you are buying in Amazon,
you buy in Amazon, right?
Yeah.
Right, so if you go and click your cart,
there will be multiple line items,
correct?
Yeah, sure.
Yeah.
Two line.
Two lines, that's the same thing, right?
The customer will put one order, right?
They can, it could be on a pallet.
On a pallet,
I can put two lines or two items or three
items, right? It doesn't matter, correct?
Yeah.
That is what it is. So in a palette,
I'm telling you how many items it is.
It could be on a palette,
it could be on a box.
So that is why you're going here and
defining what it is. You see here,
tare weight, gross weight,
all these configurations,
Yeah.
you're doing it here.
Right, the product,
you're talking about the product,
Sure.
product description, ship class, origin,
then within handling units,
there is one unit called, say,
this is an old design, right?
You might not have all of it.
You will have handling units.
How are you handling it?
Then once you're handling,
how are you putting it?
How are you going to shipping units?
right, shipping units will be,
how are you shipping those boxes, right?
I'll be putting it in a box, in a pallet.
Right.
Yeah.
Right,
so that is what I'm calling it as order
line. Make sense?
Yeah, makes sense.
So that is why you see here two in one
order I can have three lines. In this one,
there could be two lines.
If there is only one line,
you just display one line without A plus.
That's what I'm trying to tell.
Okay, got it.
Right? And okay, coming back to here,
we should have a change view like this.
So if I click here, see,
these are all the columns, right?
So these are all the fields I have,
but I cannot display.
Just like how we talked about table,
we won't be able to display all of it,
right?
I would want to display only a few things,
or probably I would want to display only
a few things.
So there's only a few selected,
but I should have option to move back and
forth between what I want and what I
don't want.
Okay, sure.
Right?
So there should be a configuration here,
like change view.
What we talked about this change view,
right? In this table on top,
we should also have for wherever there is
a table, right?
There's a lot of information like this.
Where is that? Stops product.
How does it go? Ah, product.
Wherever there are like lots of
information like this,
and we have a table structure.
Right,
I would like to prefer to have a
configuration, right? So in this order,
order is doesn't require a configuration,
but product will require a configuration
because it is more like a table structure
like this. Right, make sense?
Makes sense.
Okay, so we covered stops, orders,
product. Okay,
we will skip routing options for now.
Routing options, tender.
We'll go to cost allocation, right?
Let me see here.
Routing is a little complex. Okay.
Cost allocation. If you see here,
I have added some pictures here for your
reference.
Cost allocation is for a shipment, right?
Let me go back here for a shipment.
Once I did this,
I have the cost information, right?
In order to move.
two shipments together, which is weighing,
let's say, 5,000 pounds,
that will be something that the carrier
will be charging me, correct?
Yeah.
That is what the cost is.
That is what I'm trying to put here under
the cost section, right? Under the, sorry,
I have to move here and there.
under the cost allocation section,
that is what I'm trying to add, right?
Trying to show the user, right,
what is my cost in order to ship with
Yeah.
this particular carrier.
Okay.
Right, as a planner, I would want to know,
right,
what is the cost involved to ship with
this carrier, right?
So that is what I'm trying to add here.
Sure.
A cost allocation, we are here, right?
Okay, under, yeah, cost allocation, right?
Under the cost allocation,
That's the location, OK.
we are talking only about planned cost,
right? I've given you example,
Okay.
I just wanted to show as a table view,
right? Normally, let me go,
how do I show you?
Okay, let me show you here.
Any cost will have a base discount fuel,
right?
And there could be also additional
charges, right? Say for example.
You are asking,
we talked about stops here, right?
We talked about multi-stops, right?
Pickup, delivery.
Yeah.
So imagine customer is saying,
you might have to wait here for 30
minutes in my pickup.
Right?
Obviously the driver will charge
Yeah.
something extra, correct?
They are not just going to stay there for
Okay.
30 minutes.
Right,
that charges will be reflected here.
Got it.
in this section, right? Yeah.
Say if you see a stop of charges, SOC,
right? This charge, they will add it.
Say for example, for the by shipment,
you saw here the by shipment cost.
1000, 1080, right?
AP freight cost is 1080.
Yeah.
What is the breakup for this 1080?
Someone is asking, right, where will I go?
I'll go to cost allocation and that's
where I can see my cost breakdown.
Right? That is that.
You will come here and see that, okay,
for this order, my direct cost.
Direct cost is if I did not consolidate,
if I did not put this together, right?
If I did not put this together,
Yeah.
I shipped it directly with a carrier.
What will be my cost? Right?
That is what the direct cost is.
You just add the direct cost.
Okay.
Then, AP cost is the Desk cost.
Right? This AP freight cost.
It is this cost, right? That cost,
Okay.
I'm trying to break down and trying to
tell, say, there we had 1080.
Imagine that this is 1500.
I will say this 1500 is broken down into
Yeah.
1000. 1000 for the base rate.
Fuel is going to be 400,
discount become Odyssey is giving the
customer a discount of $100.
They're charging hazmat charges.
Okay.
It's ZC is a hazmat charge, right?
They're charging customer the hazmat
Got it.
charge for $100 because this is a hazmat
shipment, right?
And we talked about stop-off charges,
right? These are all additional charges.
It can be there, it might not be there.
But what will be there as part of the
Yeah.
cost is base and fuel will 100% be there.
Got it.
Right? Discount can be there,
may not be there as part of the cost,
right?
They can give a customer a discount,
they might not give a discount, right?
Charges, it might be there,
it might not be there.
It's all going to be based on what type
of shipment it is.
Right? Say in this particular case,
you see here, I have two orders.
Yeah.
We talked about the scenario where two
loads are put together.
Two loads are from these two orders.
Right? You see here, I've written 1,800.
So what it says is if I ship this
separately with one carrier and I ship
this one separately with another carrier,
This would have cost me 1000 and this
would have cost me 800, right?
Yeah.
That is what this direct cost is, 1800,
right? But AP cost is, if you see 1500,
1500. So I have put these two together.
So these two together is going to give me
1500. I'm just, it is my interpretation.
Right, interpretation my representation.
If you have a better way to represent
Yeah.
this information, you let me know.
Okay, sure.
Right, see,
because these two together is going to
cost me 1500,
so that is why I have 1500 represented in
both the lines, right,
against these two orders.
Sure. Makes sense.
Makes sense.
Yeah, that is why you have the same data,
but it is not that this order is going to
be charged 1500 and this order is going
to be charged 1500.
Together to move these two orders
together, the AP cost is going to be 1500.
But if they had shipped together,
it would have cost them 1800, right,
Sure.
to move these shippers,
because this shipment is going to be 1000,
this shipment is going to be 800,
so together is going to be 1800,
but by combining these two,
I have saved $300 for the customer.
Sure.
Okay.
Okay, so we covered the cost allocation.
So this is how we would,
I would probably want to see,
but whatever is the best way,
you try to put it together.
Right, so we did see cost allocation.
Next is instruction.
We'll go to see instruction.
Right?
Instruction is nothing but say on an
order, right?
Customer can give instruction.
Have you seen this on an order?
Add instruction. You see here instruction,
right? So I can put instruction mask.
Yeah.
Then.
here, BOL, right?
Let's say BOL instruction, right?
Print carrier, should print BOL, right?
So this information is there.
It's all coming from the order, correct?
Each order will have its own instruction,
correct?
Yeah.
But when we look here,
all these instructions will be
transferred to a load, right?
Order is represent,
load is representative of an order.
So load carries the order information,
but the shipment carries both the load
and load information.
So as a shipment I'm viewing,
I should see
all the instructions together. Make sense?
Yeah, makes sense.
Yeah.
These are all my instructions.
Yeah, sure.
Right? That is what.
That's why I've written here.
Each order instruction should be
displayed.
If the order has multiple instructions,
each instruction should be displayed in
sequence. Right? As you can see here.
There are multiple instructions I can add,
right? Add instructions, add instruction.
Ohh.
They keep on adding instruction.
So in an order,
Yeah.
I can have multiple instructions.
If I have 3 instructions,
I should see three lines or three set of
information represented for an order.
If I have another order here,
because that shipment is combined with
If the two loads are combined for that
order,
then I should have multiple instructions
for that particular order, right?
Sure.
If you feel that order and load can be
combined and displayed in some ways,
that is also nice, right? You can say,
like, together,
say this order is representative of this
load, right?
I didn't have that information.
What I'm talking is, right?
We are talking about order here,
but we are not trying to tell saying that
this load is representative of this order.
Yeah.
This load is representative of this order,
right? You are getting my point, right?
Yeah, Geta.
Yeah, okay. We covered instructions.
So I would want, yeah,
Seerla.
Instruction.
I would want the user to see all the
instructions. Make sense?
Yeah.
Makes sense.
Okay, history, forget about history,
I have not created that screen.
We'll talk about documents and notes,
right?
Okay.
A lot of things, sorry,
I have to tell you because in one go I
Yeah, it's too much,
but this is very helpful for me for the
tell you.
process that I performance right now in
order. This is very, very, very helpful.
Brate.
It's wonderful, amazing.
Yeah, see, for documents,
I would wanted to add,
I want to give users an option to add BOL,
right? MBOL, invoice, instructions,
others, right?
If I don't know what type of document it
is, I would classify under others.
So how I will do it is I just use the
same information, how it is in ODM.
Right, that is a document.
I call.
tracking attachments right here.
If you see here, upload attachments.
Yeah.
If I go click upload attachments,
it gives me options what I wanted to do.
I just changed these to this my
requirements, right? BOL, MBOL,
invoice instructions and others, right?
So instead of general, you put BOL.
Yeah.
Sure.
Instead of MBOL, you use, say,
instead of SLI, you use MBOL.
Instead of DGD, you use invoice, right?
Like this, you can select,
and then if you want to give instructions,
you can do, then click and upload, right?
Then each one will be one line item.
That is what I have written here, right?
Attach the documents and should support
PDF, Excel, Word, CSV,
Outlook messages format.
Once attached,
each attachment should be aligned with
Jack.
type, description, and file with link.
Yeah.
Right, on clicking the file,
the user should be able to open the
attachment on a new window.
Sure.
Right,
should have an option to delete the
attachment via UI.
That's all. It's straightforward. Right,
any questions here?
No, it's simple. It's unapploved standard.
Yeah, right.
Yeah, it's standard, right?
Internal notes.
Internal notes is more like Jira, right?
You have seen Jira, right?
Yeah.
Yeah,
that's what I put in the image of the
Jira, right? The user,
user should be able to add internal notes.
For now,
tagging of names are not required, right?
You don't have to tag names like this
because we don't have that functionality,
Okay.
right? So they can just, if I write,
if I group, my name will be available.
like Janardhana wrote at this time,
at this date and time,
what is the message? That's all.
So that the next user who is coming might
be able to go into the nodes and see what
it is.
What was the last thing that they wanted
to communicate or what they wanted to say?
That's all.
Yeah, it's simple.
Very simple, yeah. Okay.
Yeah.
Okay, so now we covered all this.
Let's see. We left, I left history.
I didn't cover.
A document is done, notes is done,
instruction, cost. I'll come to tender,
tender history.
We are not doing tender history and
history are same, right?
Forget about this for now. Tender history,
Okay.
I'll, yeah, routing is there,
routing is the next one, right?
Okay, routing is a little complicated.
I'll try to explain as much as possible.
Okay.
Right, where did it go routing?
Routing, routing, routing, routing option.
Yeah. See,
these are all the things that I would
want in the routing, right?
All the fields.
Say routing is nothing but, let's say,
we go back here, right?
Routing is nothing but options.
If I routing guide, do I have something?
Here. You see here,
what this particular order,
Yeah.
it talks about order,
but we are talking about shipment, right?
Imagine this is a shipment, right? In TMS,
this is a shipment.
Okay.
We are not going to talk about order.
Once we come into a shipment,
then it is all going to be shipments,
right? So this is a shipment number.
Inside that, I need to find a carrier.
The objective of
planning is what,
to find a carrier for my shipment,
correct?
Yeah.
Right?
So now I have already identified this,
right? But whom I have to tender to?
I know that this is my plan.
I am going to put load one and load two
together into one shipment,
but I don't know which carrier is going
to pick this one up, correct?
Yep.
Right,
so there is an option called routing
guide, right?
Routing guide is going to give me all the
set of carriers to whom I can send the
tender to. You know what is tender, right?
No.
Okay, tender is like, you know,
how do you say tender? Okay.
Okay, you are doing a, let's imagine,
you are doing a...
What do you say?
You want to do a paint job at your home,
Okay.
right? At your place,
you want to do some paint job, right?
You want to paint your entire home.
So you have identified 4 painters, right,
Okay.
who can do that job.
Okay.
Right?
You're contacting the first painter,
right? Give me a quote, right?
Will you be able to take this job?
And you will be,
you have a set of requirements, right?
Yeah.
You will say, I need to paint, I need to,
I want you to use oil paint, oil painting.
It needs to be two coats.
Then you need to scrub the walls and do
it.
And I need you to be done in one week.
Yeah.
These are your requirements, right?
You tell him.
Then he will give you a quote. Correct?
Yeah.
Right, so similarly,
you will get code from four different
painters, correct?
Oh right, yeah, I got it at that point.
Yeah,
then you will fix one painter for your
work because based on some evaluation,
correct?
Correct.
Yeah,
imagine Odyssey has already done the
pre-work, pre-work of telling what it is,
right?
Okay.
See, once you build a shipment,
you know that what is a pickup, right?
Let me go here. Once you build a shipment,
you know what is a pickup date,
delivery date, correct?
Then you know what is the origin,
which is the destination, how many miles,
Yeah.
what is the weight you're going to take,
and you know what are other information,
right?
But for what we have already done is for
this origin and destination,
I know who are all the people who can
carry that, carry the load.
Okay.
Right?
So there are four carriers who can carry
this particular load between this origin
and this destination for this date.
Sure.
Not date,
but for this origin and destination.
I know that. As an odyssey,
they have already evaluated it.
The system knows that. Right?
But I need to ask them,
Okay.
will they be able to accept it?
Yeah.
Right? That is what the tender process is.
You will send that information.
Mmmm.
You will send the entire information to
that particular carrier,
the four identity. First,
you will send the information to 1
carrier. You wait for response. Right?
If they accept it,
Okay.
you will give it immediately to them
because you already know the cost.
Alright, alright.
Right,
because you have agreed and you have,
you see here, these are all that, right?
So this particular TL,
this is the carrier.
I know that this carrier is going to
charge me $111.
Okay.
Right?
CTNS is going to say there is no rate.
Say CTNS if I do,
they are going to charge me 1908.
I would want ECHS to accept,
but I don't know whether they will accept
it.
Sure.
Right? That is what the tender does.
It will send it to EC and ECHS and wait
for the response.
Okay.
Right,
if you already know the rate and you know
what are the carries,
who will you first send it to?
Okay.
The lowest one, correct?
Sure.
Right,
because that is more lucrative for you
because you can save some money, correct?
Sure.
So that is why you send it to ECHS.
So tendering is nothing but you know who
are all the carriers,
but you are sending one by one, right?
You are asking the best carrier whom you
want to send to and ask them whether you
would be picking it up.
They would say yes or no. If they say yes,
it is accepted. If they say no,
Yeah.
You go to CPNS,
you go to the next carrier.
Sure.
Right? Then you ask the same question.
Do you want to take it or no?
They will say yes or no. If they say no,
you go to the third carrier. Like this,
you do. This is called tendering process.
All right, okay.
Right? So in tampering,
you have all this information. You see,
you have distance,
you know the transit time, you know rate,
who is the carrier, right?
And then you are sending that information
to that carrier.
So that is what I have added here.
So what are all the fields for...
Where is that product?
routing.
So what are all the fields that are
required to create a routing?
Say for example, you need a route rank,
right? Which is the first option?
Let me see if I am, do you have time?
Five minutes? I'll try to complete it in.
Okay,
Yeah, yeah.
I'll try to complete it in 5 minutes so
that it's, so that you understand what is.
Yeah, yeah.
what I am talking about.
Help.
Yeah, it's not a good option.
Here, right?
Okay.
So what it does is, you see,
this is what I was saying, right? Say,
this is the customer,
this is the shipment number, right?
This is the total weight,
how many packages are there part of the
shipment, what mode it is, right?
Then you have all these options.
Yeah.
Say all these options are,
these are the carriers whom I would want
to ask the question, yes or no?
Do you want to take this load?
Right?
I already have the cost information.
Yeah, sure.
These are part of the contract, right?
For this pickup and delivery.
What is that?
For this pickup and delivery, right?
There should be address as well somewhere.
Where is that? Yeah,
the pickup date and delivery is there.
One second, let me show you the address.
Where is that?
Turn appointments.
Maybe it is not here.
Okay, but for the pickup and delivery,
you know, which is the pickup, right?
So pickup, we talked about it.
So for that pickup and delivery address,
so these carriers are ready and these are
the agreed contract rates.
Now we have to ask the question one by
one, right?
Either this carrier will accept it or no.
right?
Sometimes this carrier might accept this
tender, right? When they accept it,
it changes to S, right?
Sure.
And what they are doing is,
I will pick up by this,
Jha.
we are sending this information to the
carrier.
You need to pick up by 820 and you need
to deliver by.
822. So you got only two days transit,
right? And your pickup time,
organisation numbers,
you can pick up between 7 A.m. and 3.30 P.
m., right? CST, right?
And you need to deliver between noon,
Yeah.
so you can deliver the entire day, right?
Anytime you can go in.
and you have to do it in CST time, right?
So you have two days transit,
total distance travel for this one is 438
miles for this origin to destination,
right?
All this are being given to the user to
Sure.
see, okay,
these are all their options and that is
what you're displaying in this particular
screen.
Right,
that is what I'm asking in the screen,
right? I've given you this example, right?
Routing option.
Okay.
So it is trying to tell the user what are
all the routing options.
You don't have to add whether it has been
accepted or not,
but you need to give this information.
You need to give them pickup,
Yeah.
you need to tell them delivery,
what is the transit, miles,
and you don't have to put this completed
or not.
But you need to have all this minimum
information, right?
That is why I have it here, right?
What are all the columns?
Okay.
Sure.
Make sense?
Makes sense.
Right? So yeah. So with this one,
it will be more like this screen, right?
This is how I would want the options to
be organized. Again,
you can have change here because they can
add, we have so many columns, right?
If you see here,
we have so many fields here for the...
routing, right? We have so many fields.
So we might not be able to display all of
the fields.
So we will be able to display only like 5
or 7 fields.
But users should have the option to add
Okay.
whichever column they want,
or if they are ready to scroll,
you should support with the scroll option
as well.
And it should have vertical scroll as
well.
Yeah.
And I don't know whether we would be able
to provide, you know,
make it as a full screen or hide it.
You know, here, if you see here,
it has an option to hide, then it, if you.
..
Hmm,
could could you could you click on on on
the uh, yeah, in the next next button?
Next one. No, the next one.
Help.
No, no,
next next to the the high button option.
I mean, in the settings, and yeah,
these settings, yeah, configure it up,
configure it.
That is for this tab.
That is for this tab, right?
Order field.
Could you click on configure order fields?
I can. I want to see.
Yeah,
and could you back to the menu and click
on?
Yeah, close this one.
I'm back to the menu. I mean,
the same button.
Uh, configure it up, click here.
Yeah.
This is these fields, right?
Yeah, this is a field. Okay, got it. Yeah.
So these are these fields, right?
What we are seeing here.
Yeah, sure. No,
it's only it's only to see there the
Right, say, for example.
options.
Yeah, these tabs, right?
That's why I kept it here. You see here.
Yeah.
This configuration is for this tab,
but each of those inside must have its
Sure.
For the stops, yeah.
own configuration, right?
If it has a lot of columns,
Yeah.
it should have its own configuration so
that the user will be able to adjust
within each of these tabs.
Each of this should have its own
configuration. You are getting it right.
Sure.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah.
Okay, sounds good.
I think I covered whatever I want to,
but we will get to this point, right?
When monitoring is next screen,
but I think this itself is a lot of thing
to do, right? To start with the design,
Yeah.
right? So,
but you just work on the wireframe.
As I told you, I've given you my best,
right? Whatever design I can do.
I tried to do it,
so I'm giving you all this option.
I'll share this deck with you so that you
can use it as a reference, right?
Yeah, could you share me this PowerPoint?
Yeah, yeah,
I'm going to say share this deck with you
so that you can use this information to
start work on your design.
Yeah, another question is,
you say that we can start with five
screen.
Which one are those five screen to start
the wireframes?
Desk screen.
Yeah.
This is a screen that you need to start.
Don't, I'm not asking you to work on this.
No,
that these requirements will come from
This is not necessary.
Steve and, yeah, this is not necessary.
This will come from Steve and Ramesh,
Okay.
right?
I want you to start working on this,
this particular, forget about, yeah,
forget you,
This is a screen.
you just put the dummy screen here,
monitor and PGA.
But this is what I require, right?
This and all this what we talked about,
right?
Each of these and how each of these.
Yeah, but this is more than,
this is more than five.
This is more than five screen.
These are internal tabs, right? Say,
for example,
Yeah,
but this is each of the each each tab is
order order will go to fetch from.
each is a screen that I need to
performance.
Right, eat.
That, yeah,
that's why I want to ask you again: how
A.
many tabs we can concentrate for the fear
efforts? I mean,
five tabs is better for me right now
because I need to work on...
Complete the orders.
Complete the the.
Products,
I think that I need to complete something
about product section and also help help
engage to complete user management
OK.
section that this is a lot of Jira
stories and and the first week.
Of March.
I will go to,
I will take a vacation for one 1 1/2
weeks.
Hey Efrain,
you should not be taking vacation Efrain.
A.
Yeah, no, no, it's necessary for me. Yeah,
it's yeah, but to be honest,
I'm just joking. We need, we need you,
we need you.
I need this day on Friday to complete
some part of tracking that.
Kathleen needs for me and also complete
the entire proposal for the final version
Yeah.
of the order creation.
Mhm.
And I think, to be to be honest,
I can start with those screens next
Tuesday.
Provide you the the screen.
I mean, until we can review.
The first screen on Wednesday and on
Tuesday, if you...
When you say first screen,
what screen is that?
I mean,
the first screen with with with all tabs.
I mean, I can, I can perform on.
To a screen.
For Wednesday, I mean,
if I start the whiteframe on Tuesday,
I think that I will have a whiteframe for.
..
two or three screen. I mean,
the first screen that we have, the table,
the tax, achievements.
all achievements and also, for example,
have the view for orders and for products,
Mhm.
I think.
Mhm.
Yeah,
I think that I can start or I will have.
Next week, Tuesday or Wednesday,
you're saying, right?
Yeah, I think that Wednesday.
So by 25th,
you will be able to give some screens,
Yeah.
correct?
Yeah,
you can I can provide you or we can we
No.
can have a call on Wednesday and cheque
everything if is this good for you.
Uh-huh.
We can continue with more one screen.
But I'm not sure that I can provide you
all those stuff at the end of the week.
I think that I can provide you maybe 3
screen.
And then I continued with the next screen
after my vacation time.
Yeah, okay. Whatever is possible,
you get started, right?
Alright.
So we can review together.
Certain things are very straightforward,
right? Say for example,
notes and attachments are very
Yeah.
straightforward. It's not that difficult,
right? So again, orders,
No, I, this is a boyfriend.
I can do that very, very... Sorry,
orders you might have already,
you need to plug in the orders.
could you repeat?
Orders, orders, I'm saying, orders,
you should be able to directly plug in
the order information,
what you already have, right? Similarly,
Yeah.
product information,
you should be able to plug in that
information, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, so that is why I'm saying,
say certain things,
one or two screens are really hard,
but like routing, like, you know,
stops in appointments might take a little
longer, right?
Because you have to create a view,
but rest, yeah,
Yeah, yeah, I said very long.
rest of the things should be
straightforward.
That's what I'm trying to say, right?
Maybe if you sit,
maybe if you sit for two, three days,
you should be able to finish it.
Okay.
I'm saying just if you work on these
alone,
I'm not saying you work on all of it, but.
..
Yeah, and yeah,
it's only because Mangesh needs need me
to provide the feedback,
and he has several UI issues that we need
to fix on on his flow, and Kathleen is is.
..
Okay, okay.
Yeah.
** *** needs our our complete our our
feedbacks. We need to complete the flow.
But when I say that he need my feedbacks,
I mean, Mangesh need my feedback,
is that I need to work on that because
some part, Mangesh can manage some part,
but at some point he can, he can.
He,
he don't have all solution or all
experience to complete the complex part
of the flow, and that's why, yeah,
and that's why I need to help him,
and also I teach him right now about some
Yeah, I understood.
part of UX, because...
I need that he will be more independent
from me and provide me and improve his
skill,
provide the right solution like a UX
designer.
I think that he can do that.
He can do that,
Mm.
but we need to work on that and he can
improve his skill.
Mm.
Yeah, but yeah,
I need time to spend with him to improve
his designs and then I have ordered and
also achievements. Yeah, that's why.
Did you finish orders?
No, this is not complete.
I need to work today.
Okay, okay.
I receive more feedbacks and I think that
I need to spend the rest of the day of
this day on order and then continue
tomorrow to...
Mhm.
To get the final version,
because on Monday we will have a
conversation of the final,
final version for order creation, yeah.
OKOK.